liagriffith.com 2019-07-22

# Privacy Policy - Lia Griffith

We respect your privacy and we are committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect about you and why, what we do with that information, and how we handle that information when you visit or make a purchase from LiaGriffith.com (the “Site”).

### Personal identification information

* * *

We will collect personal information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

We collect personal information from you in a variety of ways. If you choose to become a Monthly, Annual or Premium member of LiaGriffith.com, we will collect your name, email address and credit card details in order to process your payment and to stay in touch with you about your membership. We use Chargebee to process payments for Membership to LiaGriffith.com and to store your name, email address and credit card information. You can read more about [how Chargebee uses your Personal Information here](https://www.chargebee.com/privacy/).

If you choose to subscribe to our email newsletter, you have the option to provide your name, email address, membership information and birthdate. This information is collected and stored within our email marketing software, Mailchimp. You can read more about [how Mailchimp uses your personal information here](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

You can [opt out of email marketing anytime here ](https://liagriffith.us3.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=a5f593e2f29c97a3b3069b1a2&id=e8d7ffacc0)

We use Shopify to power our online store. If you set up an account or place an order in our online shop we will collect and store your name, email address, credit card details, billing and mailing address. You can read more about how [Shopify uses your Personal Information here](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).

### Non-personal identification information

* * *

We may collect non-personal identification information about you whenever you interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider utilized and other similar information.

We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how you use our Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

### Web browser cookies

* * *

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance your experience. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about your web use. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. Please check your browser’s help section for instructions on how to do this.

### Links

* * *

This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you, when you leave this website, to read their privacy policy as this particular privacy policy applies solely to this particular website.

### Advertisers

* * *

We use outside advertising networks and companies in order to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons in order to collect data in the ad serving process. These such cookies and/or web beacons are collected by the companies and/or advertising networks, themselves

### Google Adsense

* * *

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Third party websites

* * *

You may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of may partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Webmaster Contact Information

* * *

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding the www.liagriffith.com privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at [hello@liagriffith.com](mailto:hello@liagriffith.com)
